[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country is the art of palm reading believed to have originated?", "correct_answer": "India", "incorrect_answers": ["Greece", "Persia", "China"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what event was the opera Aida premiered?", "correct_answer": "The opening of the Suez Canal", "incorrect_answers": ["The opening of La Scala in Milan", "The opening of  the Panama Canal", "The  opening of the National Opera House in Rome"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What vitamin are lychee fruits rich in?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin C", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin D", "Vitamin A", "Vitamin E"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actress played the daughter of a Vietnam War vet, who repairs Malones mustang in the 1987 film Malone.", "correct_answer": "Cynthia Gibb", "incorrect_answers": ["Jill St. John", "Sandra Locke", "Susan St. James"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these islands is shared by three countries?", "correct_answer": "Borneo", "incorrect_answers": ["Luzon", "Ireland", "Madagascar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This physician has been trained in the diagnosis and management of kidney disease.", "correct_answer": "Nephrologist", "incorrect_answers": ["Neurologist", "Urologist", "Proctologist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During World War II, the Polish Second Corps fought bravely against the Axis forces. Which statement about the Second Corps is not true?", "correct_answer": "There was a brown bear in the corps.", "incorrect_answers": ["They fought at Monte Cassino.", "They escaped Europe by going into Iran.", "They landed on Normandy Beach an hour after the first wave hit Omaha Beach."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The area around what Italian volcano is the most densely populated volcanic region in the world, making the volcano one of the most dangerous on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Mount Vesuvius", "incorrect_answers": ["Mount Etna", "None of these", "Stromboli"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Two young women and an artist, who finds himself attracted to both of them, form one of the love triangles in this Woody Allen movie.", "correct_answer": "Vicky Cristina Barcelona", "incorrect_answers": ["Everyone Says I Love You", "Melinda and Melinda", "A Midsummer Nights Sex Comedy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This was the original title of a song, produced by Billy Davis and sung by The New Seekers, and featured in a 1971 TV commercial of Coca Cola.", "correct_answer": "Id Like to Teach the World to Sing", "incorrect_answers": ["In Perfect Harmony", "Id Like to Buy the World a Coke", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1986, this musician, famous for performing the song  Johnny B. Goode, became the first person inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.", "correct_answer": "Chuck Berry", "incorrect_answers": ["Bill Haley", "Elvis Presley", "Jerry Lee Lewis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is considered to be the final major hurdle before reaching the summit of Mt. Everest from the South Col Route?", "correct_answer": "Hillary Step", "incorrect_answers": ["First Step, Second Step and Third Step", "Kangshung face", "Lhotse face"]}]